mythoughtcounts.com 2010-05-14

# MyThoughtCounts: Share your opinion to win great prizes!

### Commitment

Ampario is an online data collection, marketing, and advertising company dedicated to providing high performance data and solutions to the Market Research community. We design, build, and distribute digital panels, products, and campaigns. In doing so we hold your privacy in the highest importance and provide this statement disclosing the privacy practices for Ampario , Ampario Media, Ampsurveys.com, and all properties in the Ampario network referred to throughout as simply Ampario. This notice will be available at all Ampario properties in which personally identifiable information is requested. By visiting Ampario, you are accepting the practices described herein. Because Ampario wants to demonstrate its commitment to your privacy, it has agreed to disclose its information practices and notify you of the following:

### The information we collect.

The information we collect helps us ensure that our services are best designed to meet your needs. We receive and store any information that you enter on any registration page, typically for contests, sweepstakes, surveys, and or other promotions. If you are giving us information in order to participate in a survey, sweepstakes, contest or other promotion, your participation is completely voluntary and you therefore have a choice whether or not to disclose this information of which some is required which we will identify and some is optional. We collect both contact and other unidentifiable information including but not limited to the following.

• First Name  
• Last name  
• Email address  
• Member Name  
• Password  
• Birthdate  
• Gender  
• Ethnicity  
• Zip code  
• Highest level of education completed  
• Total yearly family household income before taxes

**A. Contact Information**

Contact information consists of the information that we can use to contact you if, for example, you win one of the contests or promotions sponsored by Ampario and/or its affiliates and partners. This generally consists of your e-mail address, IP address and possibly your name, mailing address and telephone number. Visitors who supply Ampario with their postal address may receive periodic postal mailings with useful information from other reputable companies.

**B. Other Information**

Profile data also is collected at our site. Depending on the specific Ampario products for which a user ("User") registers, various information will be requested. We use this data to tailor the visitor's experience in the current environment and through e-mails. By obtaining this information, we can provide our Users with specific content that we think they might be interested in, according to their preferences and interests. The User may include only the information he or she feels comfortable including. However, the more information we have about a User, the more valuable the Ampario experience will be for that User.

### How is User information used?

**A. Information that you provide**

Ampario does not send unsolicited or "spam" e-mail. We use User information in a number of ways, including:

1) to invite users to surveys that match their profile;  
2) to send targeted advertising that allows us to provide our service at no cost to the Users;  
3) to send promotions and coupons based on their interests;  
4) to send targeted information to the User in the form of e-mail messages and/or direct mail;  
5) to monitor and improve its internal operations,  
6) to send Users other information about Ampario and/or its products.

When you register with Ampario, you may receive offers from us or our marketing partners. Our marketing partners may use this information to make offers to you in your areas of interest or other offers. Our marketing partners wishing to contact you either give their e-mail message to us and we deliver it to you, or with your prior permission, we provide your contact information to them so they can deliver messages directly to you. It is solely at your discretion if you choose to provide additional personally identifiable information to a marketer by making a purchase, requesting additional information, or communicating directly with the company or organization after using its website. We may also use outside companies to execute the marketing campaigns on our behalf or on behalf of some of our marketing partners. We will share your e-mail name & other information that you give us that is necessary for these third parties to provide these services. These third parties are not allowed to use personally identifiable information except for the purposes of providing these services.

**B. Automatic Information ("Cookies") and similar objects.**

We use a cookie, and or other similar objects refered to as ‘cookies’ throughout for convenience, as a piece of data stored on the User's hard drive containing information about the User. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on the Ampario Site. For instance, by setting a cookie on our site, the User would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our site. If a User rejects the cookie, he or she may still use our site. The only drawback to this is that the User will be limited in some areas of the Ampario Sites. For example, the User may not be able to participate in selected Sweepstakes, promotions, surveys, contests or monthly Drawings that take place. Cookies also can enable us to track and target the interests of our Users to enhance their experience on the Ampario Site.

You can set your browser to not accept cookies. Please be aware that by doing so certain features of the Ampario Site may not work. See your browser's documentation for more information on accepting cookies.

Ampario uses cookies to collect and store certain types of information when you interact with us in order to (i) access your account information (stored on our computers) and keep track of your points or credits; and (ii) learn what you like and, hence, to provide a more personalized experience for you. In the future, Ampario may use cookies to enable us or a merchant to track visits to and business. Ampario strongly encourages all of its partners to post their privacy policies on their sites and to adhere to the same high standards as stated herein.

**C. Log Files**

We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track User's movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. While we collect standard Apache log files, we do not use them for any purpose other than determining page views. We also collect pages visited within our database through cookies (as discussed above). This data is connected with registration information so we can determine site usage and for marketing research.

### Information Sharing.

**A. Registration Information**

As part of the registration process, we often offer you the option to take advantage of offers from our partners. Those offers are optional and you do not have to sign-up for any offers in order to participate in the main promotional offer (although you may need to check or uncheck certain boxes to do so). If you do choose to sign-up for an offer, we will share information about you with those selected partners from whom you have chosen to receive information.

When you register with Ampario, you can elect to sign up with some of our marketing partners so they may to contact you via email with their special offers. It is solely at your discretion if you choose to provide additional personally identifiable information to a marketer by making a purchase, requesting additional information, or communicating directly with the company or organization after using its website. We may share this information with a third-party advertising company in order to market more effectively to you.

We may employ other companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf (e.g., outsourced e-mail delivery companies). They have access to the User information to perform their functions, but may not use it for other purposes.

**B. Links to Other Sites**

This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site. As part of our business, we also provide links to third party sites. We encourage all of our merchants to post their privacy policies on their sites and to adhere to the same high standard as is stated here. We, however, disclaim any responsibility for the actions of these third parties. AS A RESULT, WE ENCOURAGE OUR USERS TO READ THE PRIVACY POLICIES OF THESE LINKED SITES, BECAUSE THEIR PRIVACY POLICIES MAY DIFFER FROM OURS.

**C. Protection of Ampario and Others**

We may release User or account information as is necessary to comply with the law; enforce or apply our Terms and Conditions and other agreements; or to protect the rights, property, or safety of Ampario, its subsidiaries, affiliates or partners, our Users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection.

### What Choices do I have?

**A. Choices In Disclosing Information**

Because we want our Users to feel completely comfortable using the Ampario services, we provide you with various opportunities to control how the information you provide to us will be used by us. We request information from our customer’s registration, as well as via surveys or contests or other promotions. Your participation in these activities is completely voluntary and you therefore have a choice whether or not to disclose this information. Nevertheless, certain basic information is required in order to register as a User. Information requested may include contact information, and demographic information. You also may choose whether or not to get e-mails from Ampario and whether or not to accept special offers from our partners. If you choose not to receive e-mail from Ampario we will not send you e-mail, although it may take a short time to remove your name from our database.

**B. Opting Out**

To remove your User information from our mailing list(s) so as not to receive future communications from us or to no longer receive our service, please go to: http://www.ampario.com/ and enter your email address. If you have submitted personal information under more than one e-mail account, you must make this request from each account that you have used. If you choose not to receive e-mail from Ampario we will not send you e-mail, although it may take a short time to remove your name from our database. Ampario will use commercially reasonable efforts to delete records from our mailing list when we receive requests to do so. This Privacy Policy is subject to change from time to time, so please check back periodically. Use of the services offered at this site constitutes acceptance of the terms of this Policy.

### How secure is my information?

The information we receive from or about you is stored on systems designed to prevent the loss, misuse, unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration or destruction of that information. In addition, certain of the Ampario Sites encrypt your transmission of sensitive information to it in the interest of heightened privacy protection and information integrity.

While we strive to protect your personal information, Ampario cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk. In addition, Ampario and third party Internet sites and services accessible through Ampario or parties whom we inform you are collecting data in connection with contests, games, promotions, etc., have separate privacy and data collection practices, independent of us. Ampario has no responsibility or liability for these independent policies or actions. You are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your passwords and/or any account information. Please be careful and responsible whenever you are online.

### Other Conditions of Use, Revisions

If you choose to visit one of the Ampario Sites, you consent to the information practices described herein and your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy and the Terms and Conditions for the individual site (including limitations on damages, and arbitration of disputes). You agree that Ampario's liability for any breach of this privacy policy shall be limited to the value of the transactions or services provided to you by Ampario to the extent such claim is not otherwise barred by our Terms and Conditions. You also agree that you have provided notice to, and obtained consent from, any third party individuals whose personal data you supply to Ampario with regard to: (a) the purposes for such third party's personal data have been collected; (b) the intended recipients or categories of recipients of the third party's personal data; (c) which of the third party's data are obligatory and which data, if any, are voluntary; and (d) how the third party can access and, if necessary, rectify the data held about them.

You further acknowledge that Ampario operates in the United States. You agree (i) to permit Ampario to transmit and use your User information anywhere necessary, including across international boundaries, to affect the services and transactions provided by this Site; and (ii) that such use by Ampario shall be subject to the terms and conditions stated in this Privacy Statement and our Terms and Conditions.

Ampario may transfer, sell or assign information concerning your use of this Site, including without limitation, personally identifiable information that you provide and other information concerning your use of the Site, to third parties, as a result of a sale, merger, consolidation, changing control, transfer of substantial assets, reorganization or liquidation of Ampario.com.

Ampario or its successors and assigns may amend the terms and conditions of the Privacy Policy at any time, or substitute a different Agreement by posting a revised version, on the Ampario Sites. Please refer to our site periodically for updates. Amendments shall become effective upon posting. As we continue to develop our business, we might sell or buy certain assets. In such transactions, customer information generally is one of the transferred business assets. If Ampario or its assets are acquired, customer information will of course be one of the transferred assets.

### Contact Information:

If you are not in agreement with the terms of this Policy, please unsubscribe from Ampario; email [info@ampario.com](mailto:info@ampario.com) or write to us at Ampario, 10567 Jefferson Blvd. Culver City, CA 90232 and request to be removed.

If you feel that Ampario is not abiding by its posted privacy policy, please email [info@ampario.com](mailto:info@ampario.com) or write us at Ampario, 10567 Jefferson Blvd. Culver City, CA 90232.
